[Music]
[Applause]
Hello, I'm Dina Junarsi Setiawan.  I'm
from Bandung.  I have been
with FD since
2011. My FD Story.  In 2024, I
handled a lot of claims from
customers.  But with FWD's
digital support, I've been helped a lot
.  But perhaps my suggestion is
good communication between FWD and the provider and
of course with the hospital.  Because
with good communication, the tagline
of FWD Celebrate Riving is
truly felt by customers and
by him.
As per my motto, I am happy
to help.  I want to make this happen
with EVD.  Of course, with the support of FD
from its digital system, the support is
more understandable,
the application is easier, so it is in line with
the tagline of FPD Celebrate Living,
so I can help many more
Indonesian families, even more
.
sw